A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- VI. Development Projects and Initiatives Files, 2001-2005., Extent: 6.25 cubic feet (16 boxes). (Box 83-98)
  Subjects found in the Projects and Initiatives-Alphabetical section include: Virginia Economic Strike Force, Economic Development Strategic Plan ("One Virginia-One Future"), Electricitiy Deregulation, Export Task Force, Higher Education Summitt, Housing, Virginia Horse Center, NASCAR Hall of Fame, Olmstead implementation, Virginia Tech Economic Development, Water, and Wine.
  Notable documents filed under Projects and Initiatives-Alphabetical include: 25 January 2002 memorandum from Michael J. Schewel to Governor Warner outlining a proposal as to how the Economic Crisis Strike Force would be deployed (b84, f6); Blueprint for the Economic Crisis Strike Force-Draft, 18 February 2002 (b84, f6); 2 January 2002 memorandum from James W. Dyke, Jr. at McGuireWoods to Secretary of Commerce and Trade-Designate, Michael J. Schewel providing a status report on baseball, Emerging Business Forum and the 2012 Olympics (b85, f1); meeting materials and notes for One Virginia, One Future Steering Committee Meeting, 8 October 2002 (b85, f3); meeting materials, notes and invitations for One Virginia, One Future Steering Committee Meeting, 14 August 2002 (b85, f4); 23 December 2003 memorandum from Bill Murray to Governor Warner outling electricity deregulation and associated issues that may be addressed druing the 2003 legislative session (b86, f1); 8 October 2003 memorandum from Michael J. Schewel to Bob Blue on Schewel's thoughts on the proposed rate cap extension (b86, f2); meeting notes and memorandums related to rate cap extension, 2003-2004 (b86, f5); agenda's meeting notes and documents related to Governor Warner's export task force on Virginia Agriculture and Forestry products, 2004 (b87, f3-4); meeting and follow-up materials related to the 20 May 2004 Forestry Industry Summit (b87, f6); copy of Virginians Racing for the NASCAR Hall of Fame Proposal, May 2005 and copy of Economic Impact of NASCAR Hall of Fame on Henrico County, Richmond Metro Area and the State of Virginia, 21 June 2005 (b90, f6 and b91, f1); and 9 February 2003 memorandum from Maurcie Jones to Governor Warner proposing the creation of an Urban Policy Task Force (b94, f2).
  Subjects found in the Projects and Initiatives-Regional section include: Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission.
  - Projects and Initiatives-Alphabetical
    - AFL-CIO, 2002 and 2004 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Academy Funds, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Adult Education, 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - American Type Culture Collection/George Mason University Lease, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Broadband, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Concept Paper, 2002-2003 (part one) (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Concept Paper, 2002-2003 (part two) (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Crossroads Rural Entrepreneurial Institute, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Day of Rest, 2004-2005 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Disaster Recovery Task Force Activities, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Distressed Area Incentive, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - EMTSAC, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Economic Crisis Strike Force, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Economic Development Material, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Economic Development Material, 2002-2005 (part two) (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Economic Development Material, 2002-2005 (part three) (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Economic Development Material, 2002-2005 (part four) (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Economic Development Material, undated (part five) (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2002 (part one) (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2002 (part two) (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Economic Development Strategic Plan, 2002 (part three) (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Education Commission Data, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Electricity Deregulation
      - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (part one) (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (part two) (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2004 (part three) (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - SB 651, Meetings, 16 March 2004 and 8 April 2004 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Rate Cap Extension, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Electricity Restructuring Regulation, 2002-2003 (part one) (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Electricity Restructuring Regulation, 2002-2003 (part two) (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - ESOPs (Employee Stock Ownership Plan), 2002 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Estate Taxes, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Export Task Force, 2004 (part one) (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Export Task Force, 2004 (part two) (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Food Stamp Employment and Training Program (FSET), 2003 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Forestry Industry Summit, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Free Trade/NAFTA, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 2002 and 2005 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Georgia Initiative, 2002-2003 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Good News Initiatives, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Growth Management Initiatives, 2002-2003 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Higher Education Summit, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Higher Education Summit, 2002-2005 (part two) (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Highland New Wind Development, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Housing
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Housing Issues, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Horse Center, 2003-2005 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Howard Hughes Medical Institute, 2003-2005 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Information Technology
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (part two) (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (part three) (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Technology Projects for Commerce and Trade, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - IT Projects, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Stafford Business and Tech Park Authority, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - IT Data for Due Diligence Project, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - I-81 Issues, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Advanced Learning and Research, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Iraq Task Force, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - JLARC, 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Jobs for Virginia, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Middle College, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - National Governors Association (NGA), 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Nanotechnology in Virginia, 2002-2004 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - NASCAR Hall of Fame, 2005 (part one) (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - NASCAR Hall of Fame, 2005 (part two) (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - NASCAR Hall of Fame, 2005 (part three) (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - National Museum of the U.S. Army, 2002-2004 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - New College of Virginia, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - New Markets Tax Credits, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - NOx Credits, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Olmstead Plan, 2002-2005 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Outsourcing, 2004-2005 (part one) (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Outsourcing, 2004-2005 (part two) (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Planning District Commission, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - REAP (Rural Economic Analysis Program), 2002 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Regional Competitiveness Act, 2003-2004 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Rest Area Privatization, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Route 28 Freeway, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Route 29 Summit, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Route 288, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - STARS (Statewide Agencies Radio System), 2003-2005 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Self-Help Credit Union, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Smart Growth Management, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Society of Plastics Industry, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Sprawl, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - State Corporation Commission, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Summit Case Appeal, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Tax on Federal Contracting, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Tech Zone, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Tipping Fee Issues, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Unemployment Trust Fund
      - Records, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Records, 2002 (part two) (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Records, 2002 (part three) (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Extended Benefits Agreement, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Employment Commmission, Reed Act, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Virginia Employment Commission, Request for Proposals, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Trust Fund Study, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Virginia Unemployment Funds, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Virginia Employment Commission, Unemployment Rates, 2002-2004 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Universities Space Research Association, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Urban Strategies, 2002-2003 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - US Airways, 2003-2004 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Virginia-Africa Business Council, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Business-Education Partnership (VBEP), 2002-2003 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU), 2002 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (VEI), 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Lottery, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Economic Bridge, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Tech-Economic Development
      - Meetings, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Meetings, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Meetings, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (part one) (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (part two) (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (part three) (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Performing Arts Foundation, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Virtual University, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Water
      - General, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Drinking Water, 2002 and 2004 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Waste Water Disposal, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Wine
      - Governor's Wine Study Group, 2002-2003 (part one) (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Governor's Wine Study Group, 2002-2003 (part two) (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Projects and Initiatives-Regional
    - Alleghany County, 2003-2004 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox County, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Augusta County, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Brunswick County, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Buchanan County, Allegheny Energy Supply Project, 2001-2002 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Charlottesville, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Chesterfield County, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Danville, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Danville (Dimon), 2002-2005 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Emporia/Greenville, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Hampton Roads, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Hampton Roads, 2003-2005 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Hampton Roads, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Hampton Roads Economic Development, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Heartland Region Economic Development, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Isle of Wight County, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Louisa County, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Lynchburg/Bedford, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Follow-Up Memo, 2003-2004 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - New Economy Strategies, Federal Funding of Virginia's 21st Century Economy, undated (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Northern Neck, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Northern Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Northern Virginia, Fairfax County BioAccelerator, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Peninsula Alliance for Economic Development, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, undated (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Rural Virginia Prosperity Commission, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Southside Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Southside Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - Southside Virginia Announcements, 2002-2004 (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Southside Virginia Delegate Meeting, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - Southside Virginia, Henry County, 2001-2002 (Box 97, Folder 36)
    - Southside Virginia, Roanoke Valley, undated (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - Southside Virginia, Russell County, undated (Box 97, Folder 38)
    - Southside Virginia, Smyth County, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 39)
    - Southside Virginia, Toyota Casting Project, 2002-2003 (Box 97, Folder 40)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 41)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 2004-2005 (Box 97, Folder 42)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development Issues, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 43)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development Issues, Lee County, 2002-2005 (Box 97, Folder 44)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 45)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 2004 (Box 97, Folder 46)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development Issues, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, VEDP, 2003-2004 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Staunton, 2002-2004 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Tappahannock/Essex County, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Coalfield Economic Development Authority, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Coalfield Economic Development Authority, 2002-2003 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Coalfield Economic Development Authority, 2002-2003 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Coalfield Economic Development Authority, Site Study, undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
- VII. Company Files - Prospects and Development, 1994-2005., Extent: 1.40 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 99-102)
  The Company Files-Prospects and Development series is housed in four archival boxes and is divided into two sections: Allen and Gilmore Administration (accession 42293) and Warner Administration (accession 42417). The records are arranged alphabetically within each section. This series contains reference material pertaining to economic development during the Governor Mark Warner's Administration. It includes information on the companies who were business prospects, as well as economic materials.
  Notable Subjects found in the Company Files-Warner Administration section include: Governor Warner's meeting with Ford Motor Company officials in Norfolk in 2003 (b100, 13); Governor Warner's meeting with Jet Blue executives in 2003 (b101, f1); and records related to Philip Morris' relocation to Richmond, 2003-2005 (b101, f9-11).
  - Allen and Gilmore Administrations (Accession 42293)
    - BTM, Inc. (Browning Transport Management, Inc.), Memo of Agreement, 1998-2002 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Cadence, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Cardinal Glass, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Dupont, 1999-2001 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Ericsson GE (Lynchburg), 1994-2000 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Motorola, 1997-2001 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Walmart (James City County), 1998-2000 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - West Creek, 1994-1998 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Westvaco, 1998-2000 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Williamsburg Crossroads, 1997-1999 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Bering Truck Corp., 1998 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Bertha Corp., 2000 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - OrangeX, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Project Blue Bell, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Project K, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Project Slate, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Scalamandre Silks, Inc., 2000 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Siemens Automotive Corp., 1999 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - SPX Corporation, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Warner Administration (Accession 42417)
    - Airports, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - America Online, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Alcoa, 2002-2003 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Alcoa Wheel Products, Lebanon, Virginia, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Allstate, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Browning Project, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Capps Shoe Company, 2005 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - C3-Creativity Incubator Document, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Creative Cities Celebrations, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Dan River, Inc., 2004 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - ED South (Secondary Education Loans), 2004 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Elegba Folklore Society, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Ford Motor Company, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Gravity Games, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Jet Blue, 2002-2003 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - JETRO (Japan External Trade Organization), 1994-2002 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - KIA Motors, 2003-2004 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Leisure Publishing Parkway Proposal, 2002 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Lockhead Martin, 2005 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Maersk, 2001-2005 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Micron (Project Rock), 2004 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - NIMBUS Jets, 2002 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Philip Morris, 2003-2005 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Philip Morris, 2004-2005 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Philip Morris, 2005 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Pillowtex, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Skilltek, 2002 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Smithfield Foods, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Travelocity, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Urban Light Works, 2002 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Verizon-Project R, 2002-2004 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Verizon-Project R, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Volvo, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- VIII. Governor's Opportunity Fund Files, 2001-2006., Extent: 2.75 cu. ft. (6 boxes) (Box 103-108)
  The Governor's Opportunity Fund Files series is housed in 6 archival boxes and is arranged alphabetically. This series contains general correspondence, proproals and approved Governor's Opportunity Fund listings and files, pertaining to economic development during the Governor Mark Warner's Administration. The files usually contain fund requests from the Virginia Economic Developement Partnership and/or memorandums from Secretary Schewel to Governor Warner requsting approval of grants. In a few instances, the name of the company is not listed; only the project's code name is used (ex. Project Spyglass). Also included are projects funded by the Virginia Investment Partnership, Tobacco Regional Opportunity Fund, or some combination.
  The Governor's Opportunity Fund is a pool of discretionary funds available to the Governor to secure a business location or expansion project in Virginia. Grants are awarded to localities on a local matching basis with the expectation that the grant will result in a favorable location decision for the Commonwealth. The Virginia Investment Partnership is a discretionary performance incentive to encourage continued capital investment by Virginia companies.
  - Governor's Opportunity Fund
    - Project Abbatron, Lee County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - ABB Transformers, Inc., Bland County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Acadia Polymers, Inc., Lynchburg, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - AES Corporation (Project Sunshine), Arlington County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Aerojet, Orange County, 2003-2004 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - AFG Industries, Inc., Washington County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Project Ajax, Stafford County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Albon Engineering and Manufacturing Plc, Russell County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Alcan Packaging, Inc., Henry County/Danville, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Amcor PET Packaging, Wythe County, 2005-2006 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - American Funds Service Company, Chesapeake, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - American Plastics, Inc., Greensville County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - American Woodmark Corporation, Inc., Smyth County and Washington County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Amerigroup Corporation, Virginia Beach, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - AmerLink, Ltd., Carroll County, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Arkay Packaging Corporation, Botetourt County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Atlanta Pulp and Paper, LLC, Brunswick County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Aurora Automotive Systems, Martinsville, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - AVID Medical Inc., James City County, 2005-2006 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Axiom Technologies, Inc., Martinsville, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Barber and Ross Company, Frederick County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Barr Laboratories, Inc., Bedford County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Bronx (Project Liberty I), Orange County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - BioPort (Project Shield), Prince William County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Blue Ridge Wood Products, Tazewell County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Bluestone Industries, Blacksburg, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - BNA (Bureau of National Affairs), Arlington County, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Boar's Head Provisions Company, Petersburg, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Boehringer Ingelheim Chemicals, Inc., Petersburg, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - BondCote Corporation, Pulaski County, 2004-2005 (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Brown Foundry, Appomattox County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Bureau of National Affairs, Arlington County, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Capital Group Companies-American Funds, Chesapeake, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - Carbone Kirkwood LLC, Prince Edward County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - Cardinal Glass Industries, Roanoke County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - Care Rehab and Orthopaedic Products, Inc., Charlotte County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - Project CARECO (Amerigroup), Virginia Beach, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - CarMax, Goochland County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Carry-On Trailer Corporation, Westmoreland County, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Celanese Acetate LLC, Giles County, 2003-2004 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Crexon Microtechnologies, Henry County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - CGI-AMS, Russell County, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - CT Technologies, Inc., Pulaski County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Clinch River Forest Products, Tazewell County, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - CMA CGM, Norfolk, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - Project COE (General Dynamics Armament and Technical Products), Smyth County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 46)
    - Comcast Cable Communications, Inc., Prince William County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 47)
    - Consolidated Glass and Mirror Corporation, Galax, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 48)
    - Corporate Executive Board, Arlington County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 49)
    - Cost Plus, Isle of Wight County, 2003-2004 (Box 103, Folder 50)
    - Creative Playthings, Emporia, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 51)
    - CRESA, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 52)
    - CTSI, Franklin County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 53)
    - Project David, Greater Richmond, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 54)
    - Decoma International, Inc., Hampton, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 55)
    - Delta Star, Inc., Lynchburg, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 56)
    - Diversified Information Technologies, Orange County, 2005-2006 (Box 103, Folder 57)
    - R.R. Donnelley and Sons, Lynchburg, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 58)
    - Double Shot, Isle of Wight County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 59)
    - EIT, Inc., Danville, 2005 (Box 103, Folder 60)
    - EMATS, Tazewell County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 61)
    - EMCO Enterprises, Inc., Page County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 62)
    - Express Scripts, Danville, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 63)
    - Flowers Baking Company, Washington County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 64)
    - Flowers Baking Company, Wythe County, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 65)
    - Food Tech International, Inc., Greensville County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 66)
    - Ford Motor Company, Frederick County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 67)
    - Project FPL, Chesapeake, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 68)
    - Franklin Building Systems, Franklin County, 2004 (Box 103, Folder 69)
    - Fuji Kiko Co., Ltd., Wise County, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 70)